Southern California Women for Understanding (SCWU) collection, 1975-1999
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Board of directors., 1975-1993.; Series 1.; 87.0 folders
  - Judi Doyle papers., 1978-1987.; Subseries 4.; 33.0 folders
    - Treasurer's reports., 1981-1987.; 5 folders (Box 2, Folders 38 - 42)
      Folder 38: 1981-1982
      Folder 39: 1983-1984
      Folder 40: 1985-1986
      Folder 41: 1987
      Folder 42: undated
- Administrative files., 1979-1994.; Series 2.; 18.0 folders
  Contains human resources files, correspondence, clippings, beta video cassettes, audio cassettes, photographs, and promotional print materials and objects.
  Documents are arranged by format.
  - Central administrative records., 1979-1994.; 7 folders (Box 2, Folders 43 - 49)
    Folder 43: Personnel committee (1980-1994)
    Folder 44: Personnel instructions (1979-1982)
    Folder 45: Employees (1980-1985)
    Folder 46: Contracting members and participating accounts (1979-1980)
    Folder 47: Volunteer task force (1980)
    Folder 48: Facilities (1980-1985)
    Folder 49: Letterhead (1979-1982)
    Folder 45 includes two 3x5 black and white photographs of Jean Conger, Executive Director, and one 8x11 print of unidentified employee. Folder 48 contains ten black and white 3x5 photographs of the West Hollywood SCWU office and staff, four color 3x5 photographs of members during the moving process, and four 8x11 black and white photographs of SCWU meeting locations.
  - Correspondence., 1981-1989.; 8 folders (Boxes 2 - 3, 16, Folders 50 - 52, 1 - 5)
    Folder 50: 1981
    Folder 51: 1982
    Folder 52: 1983
    BOX 3
    Folder 1: 1984
    Folder 2: 1985
    Folder 3: 1986
    Folder 4: 1988
    Folder 5: 1989
    BOX 16
    Folder 3: Correspondence, oversized card from LGRC Board of Directors (1982)
    Materials originally contained in two three-ring binders labeled "Correspondence." Folders have been divided and labeled according to the binder dividers.
  - Clippings., 1986-1988.; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Miscellaneous., 1984-1985.; 1 folder (Boxes 3,15, Folder 36)
    Contains a Project 10 leaflet, an SCWU leaflet on "Lesbians: Low risk for AIDS, a leaflet of the SCWU song, handwritten notes on businesses, event details, and SCWU members.
    One Betamax videocassette labeled "SCWU 9/22/85 TAM/CLAUD Tape 3."
    One audio cassette labeled "Feb 6 includes 1st tape and reconstruction of 2nd tape."
    One audio cassette labeled "Sophia's song (2 min)."
  - Promotional materials., undated.; 1 visor, 1 multimedia collage (Boxes 14,16, Folder 1)
    BOX 14
    Folder 1: One plastic lavendar SCWU visor printed with SCWU logo and feet design with black and white cloth band.
    Folder 4: One collage poster with original SCWU newsletter clippings on the 1981 Christopher Street gay pride parade and photographs of SCWU members, one 4.25x10" black and white photograph of SCWU members holding banner in the parade and one color polaroid print of Judi Doyle, Robbi Simon, Renee Scarnagi Audrey Prosser, Peggy Hargrove, and Marty Ruby.
- Financial records., 1975-1990.; Series 3.; 34.0 folders
  Contains bank statements, budgets, invoices, documentation on membership dues, financial procedures, Internal Revenue Service paperwork, and treasurer's reports.
  Folders are arranged in alphabetical order.
  - Bank statements., 1978-1980.; 3 folders (Box 3, Folders 6 - 8)
    Folder 6: 1978
    Folder 7: 1979
    Folder 8: 1980
  - Budgets., 1975-1990.; 14 folders (Box 3, Folders 9 - 21, 30)
    Folder 9: 1975-1976
    Folder 10: 1977
    Folder 11: 1978
    Folder 12: 1979
    Folder 13: 1980
    Folder 14: 1981
    Folder 15: 1982
    Folder 16: 1983-1984
    Folder 17: 1985
    Folder 18: 1986
    Folder 30: 1988
    Folder 19: 1989
    Folder 20: 1990
    Folder 21: undated
  - Insurance., 1980-1981.; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Invoices., 1979, 1986.; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Lease., 1980.; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Memberships., 1979.; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous., 1979-1981.; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 26)
    Receipts (advertisements in The Lesbian Tide and Alcoholism Center for Women), handwritten notes, letter from Impressions Gallery, and Articles of Incorporation certified by the California Secretary of State.
  - Procedures., 1980-1981.; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Receipts., 1979.; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Tax exempt status., 1980-1981.; 1 folder (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Treasurer's reports., 1977-1985.; 4 folders (Box 3, Folders 31 - 34)
    Folder 31: 1977-1978
    Folder 32: 1980
    Folder 33: 1981-1982
    Folder 34: 1984-1985
- Committees., 1976-1994.; Series 4.; 107.0 folders
  SCWU was largely sustained through the work of its various committees - activities, communications, education, fundraising, membership, and research. These committees planned, publicized, funded, fueled membership and research that powered the social and educational activities that furthered the educational mission of SCWU. The material contained in this series gives insight to the inner workings of these committees and the events and projects produced under their auspices.
  Sub-series are arranged in alphabetical order.
  - Activities., 1977-1994.; Subseries 1.; 5.0 folders
    Documents were originally contained in a three-ring-binder separated by dividers labeled by event type. Each folder contains a divider section of the original binder with the exception of "Political and cultural events." This folder contains flyers found in other parts of the collection that did not fit into the event types found in the three ring binder.
    Contains the minutes and planning notes of the Activities Committee as well as event flyers.
    - Reports, rosters, memorandum., 1977-1983.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Material arranged in a three ring binder. Folders have been divided and labeled according to the binder dividers.
    - Parties and dances., 1977-1994.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Mountain, park, beach, pool events., 1978-1986.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Weekend retreats., 1979-1992.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Political and cultural events., 1983-1993.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Communications., 1977-1991.; Subseries 2.; 13.0 folders
    The documents in the first seven folders were originally contained in a three-ring-binder separated by dividers labeled by subject. Each folder contains a divider section of the original binder. The "Circular letters" and "Flyers non-SCWU" contain material found in other parts of the collection that did not fit into the categories in the three ring binder.
    Contains a list of media resources (people and organizations), publicity materials protocol, circular letters, and flyers sent by SCWU on behalf of ally organizations.
    - Resources., 1979-1985.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Forms., 1977-1985.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Gay/lesbian media., 1977-1983.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Other media., 1978-1983.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Procedures., 1980-1985.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Advertisements and press releases., 1979-1983.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Lesbian yellow pages., undated.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Circular letters., 1989-1994.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Flyers, non-SCWU., 1984-1991.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Mailing list manager backups., undated. (Box 14)
      Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
      Two 5.25 inch floppy discs.
      Special equipment or further processing may be required for viewing. To access digital materials you must notify the reference desk in advance of your visit.
  - Education., 1976-1994.; Subseries 3.; 55.0 folders
    Folders are arranged in alphabetical order and chronological order, where possible.
    This series contains materials related to the events and projects executed by the Education Committee. Some of the most notable events include the Receptions for Understanding, Special Interest Programs, and the annual Lesbian Rights Award Dinners which honored luminary lesbian artists, writers, activists, and politicians. "Achieving Educational Objectives" highlights the early educational events of SCWU. This series also contains photographs, audio cassettes, and a beta video cassette.
    - Achieving educational objectives., 1976-1985.; 11 folders (Box 5, Folders 3 - 13)
      Folder 3: 1976-1977
      Folder 4: 1979-1980
      Folder 5: 1981-1982
      Folder 6: 1983-1984
      Folder 7: Major educational events (1977)
      Folder 8: Major educational events (1978)
      Folder 9: Major educational events (1979)
      Folder 10: Major educational events (1981)
      Folder 11: Major educational events (1982)
      Folder 12: Major educational events (1983)
      Folder 13: Events with other organizations (1981-1985)
    - Lesbian rights award dinners., 1979-1994.; 31 folders, 1 1/2" open reel (Boxes 9,14, Folders 7 - 37)
      BOX 9 Folder 7: Awardees Del Martin and Phyllis Lyon (1979)
      Folder 8: Publicity (1979-1980)
      Folder 9: Planning (1979-1980)
      Folder 10: Invitations (1979)
      Folder 33: Photographs (1979)
      Folder 34: Publicity (1983)
      Folder 11: Planning (1983)
      Folder 12: Invitations and program (1983)
      Folder 35: Photographs
      Folder 13: Publicity (1986)
      Folder 14: Planning (1985-1986)
      Folder 15: Program (1986)
      Folder 16: Photographs (1986)
      Folder 17: Publicity (1987)
      Folder 18: Planning (1987)
      Folder 19: Invitations (1987)
      Folder 20: Publicity
      folder 21 Program (1988)
      Folder 22: Publicity (1989)
      Folder 23: Program (1989)
      Folder 24: Publicity (1990)
      Folder 25: Program (1990)
      Folder 26: Publicity (1991)
      Folder 27: Program (1991)
      Folder 36: Display materials (undated)
      Folder 37: Correspondence (1991)
      Folder 28: Publicity (1992)
      Folder 29: Program (1992)
      Folder 30: Publicity (1993)
      Folder 31: Program (1993)
      Folder 32: Publicity (1994)
      BOX 14 One betamax video cassette labeled "Interview with Del and Phyllis by Myra Riddell (September 1979)." Recorded on Sony Video Tape V-30H. Box is labeled as "copied to VHS Jul 82." Unknown if tape is CV or AV format.
      For information on the Lesbian Rights Dinner (1981), see Boxes 10, 11, 15, and 16.
    - Minutes., 1983-1986.; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 14)
      Minutes and notes collected by June Mazer.
    - National Organization of Women Certificate of Achievement., 1981.; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 15)
      Alice Paul Certificate of Feminist Achievement presented to Southern California Women for Understanding for Advancement of Feminist Goals (August 22, 1981)
    - Receptions for understanding., 1978.; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Slide show on healthcare., 1979-1980.; 6 folders (Boxes 10,15, Folders 1 - 6)
      BOX 10
      Folder 1: Minutes (1980)
      Folder 2: Stories (1980)
      Folder 3: Proposal outlines (undated)
      Folder 4: Scripts (1980)
      Folder 5: Grant (1981)
      Folder 6: Resources (1979-1983)
      One audio cassette labeled "Slide comm. 3rd mtg 4/80"
    - Special interest groups., 1980-1985.; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Special interest programs., 1980-1985.; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 8)
      Bound red volume labeled "S.I.P.'s"
    - Weekend of Lesbian Culture., 1980-1981.; 4 folders (Boxes 10 - 11, 15, 16, Folders 9 - 12, 1 - 3)
      Folder 9: Elsa Gidlow (1980-1981)
      Folder 10: Film - Word Is Out (1980-1981)
      Folder 11: Poetry reading (1980)
      Folder 12: Lesbian rights award dinner (1980-1981)
      BOX 11
      Folder 1: Reception - lesbian history (1980-1981)
      One audio cassette labeled "Elsa Gidlow - reading from Sapphic songs" over KPFA, Interviewed by Padraigin McGillicuddy, Drama and Literature, September 20, 1982."
      Folder 1: Exhibit materials - 3 pins SCWU, SCWU pamphlets, Lesbian Low Risk for AIDS High Risk for Discrimination Conference Packet (1977), 5 display boards about SCWU, and rubber stamp with SCWU 13719 Ventura Bl. ste. D
      Folder 2: SCWU t-shirt
      Folder 3: Correspondence (1982)
  - Fundraising., 1976-1990.; Subseries 4.; 3.0 folders
    Contains material related to the events and planning by the Fundraising Committee.
    - Circular letters and flyers., 1976-1990.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence., 1979-1988.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Reports and memorandum., 1976-1985.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Membership., 1976-1994.; Subseries 5.; 3.0 folders
    Contains member rosters as well as material related to the events and planning by the Membership Committee.
    - Circular letters and flyers., 1977-1994.; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Membership lists., 1977-1994.; 1 folder (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Minutes and memorandum., 1976-1983.; 1 folder (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Research., 1977-1988.; Subseries 6.; 28.0 folders
    Folders are arranged by alphabetical order.
    Contains material related to the early research projects of the Research Committee. One of the most notable projects was the "Personal profile questionnaires" by which SCWU members were surveyed on their lifestyles. The "Data" folders contains the original surveys. The "Lesbian profile manuscript review contains the data analysis by members of the Research Committee. The sub-series also contains minutes, grant applications, flyers, notes, and materials on other research projects.
    - Correspondence., 1982-1988.; 2 folders (Box 11, Folders 2 - 3)
      Folder 2: General (1982-1988)
      Folder 3: Personal profile questionnaires (undated)
    - Data., 1977-1988.; 12 folders (Boxes 11 - 12, Folders 4 - 12, 1 - 3)
      Folder 4: Computer run (undated)
      Folder 5: Correlations to consider (undated)
      Folder 6: Personal profile questionnaires, #1-20 (1977-1978)
      Folder 7: Personal profile questionnaires, #21-40 (1977-1978)
      Folder 8: Personal profile questionnaires, #41-60 (1977-1978)
      Folder 9: Personal profile questionnaires, #61-80 (1977-1978)
      Folder 10: Personal profile questionnaires, #81-101 (1977-1978)
      Folder 11: Personal profile questionnaires, unnumbered (1977-1978)
      Folder 12: Profile reports data (1977-1978)
      BOX 12
      Folder 1: Data analysis by Judy Tupac (1984)
      Folder 2: Data dissemination (1981-1988)
      Folder 3: Dictionary data - Medical diagnoses and cause of death (undated)
      Folder 13: Preliminary analyses (1982)
      Folder 17: Raw data, interim version (undated)
      Folder 18: Raw data, correct version (undated)
    - Flyers., 1986.; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Future research ideas., 1981.; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Grant applications., 1983.; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Lesbian montage: health and stress presentation., 1986.; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Lesbian profile manuscript review., 1988.; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Literature reviews., 1981-1982.; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Los Angeles Lesbians: A Survey manuscript., 1983.; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Math., 1985.; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Minutes and memoranda., 1978-1986.; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Publicity., 1982.; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 14)
      Contains a comparative analysis of SCWU's research data with other studies.
    - Questionnaires., undated.; 2 folders (Box 12, Folders 15 - 16)
      Folder 15: Blank (undated)
      Folder 16: Drafts (undated)
    - Resources., 1983-1984.; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Serious health problems, question #74., undated.; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Standard measures., undated.; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Research discs., 1980-1988. (Box 14)
      13 5.25 inch floppy disks.
- Newsletters., 1976-1999.; Series 5.; 58.0 folders
  The Newsletters series primarily consists of an incomplete run of the SCWU newsletter. Volumes 1-13, 15, and 19 are complete (1977-1989, 1991, 1995). With the exception of volumes 15 and 19, the newspaper collection wanes in the 1990s. The newsletter covers the life and activities of the organization and its members. The "Herstories" column which begins in the March 1979 issue of the newsletter highlights the life history of a lesbian woman. With some exception, most featured women are SCWU members. Part one of the research data from the personal profile questionnaires was published in the December/January 1981-82 issue; the remainer of the research findings were published in subsequent issues. The newsletters also contain event listings and a short update from each area chapter chair. The bound copies of the newsletter that were donated by June Mazer, former newsletter editor, are meticulously organized and annotated. The "Newsletter retrospective" was originally a three ring binder compiled by June Mazer which highlights the challenges and evolution of the newsletter through her notes and annotations. The series also contains clippings, logo design, galleys, and the planning materials for the tenth anniversary issue which includes an audio cassette tape of the planning meeting.
  Folders are arranged in alphabetical order. Newsletters and galleys are arranged in chronological order.
  - Clippings., 1981-1989.; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Clippings from SCWU newsletters
  - Galleys., 1981-1985.; 22 folders (Box 8, Folders 1 - 22)
    Folder 1: Volume 5 Number 6 (December 1981-January 1982)
    Folder 2: Volume 6 Number 1 (February-March 1982)
    Folder 3: Volume 6 Number 2 (April-May 1982)
    Folder 4: Volume 6 Number 4 (August-September 1982)
    Folder 5: Volume 6 Number 5 (October-November 1982)
    Folder 6: Volume 6 Number 6 (December 1982-January 1983)
    Folder 7: Volume 7 Number 1 (February-March 1983)
    Folder 8: Volume 7 Number 2 (April-May 1983)
    Folder 9: 7th Anniversary Issue (May 1983)
    Folder 10: Volume 7 Number 3 (June-July 1983)
    Folder 11: Volume 8 Number 2 (April-May 1984)
    Folder 12: Volume 8 Number 3 (June-July 1984)
    Folder 13: Volume 8 Number 4 (August-September 1984)
    Folder 14: Volume 8 Number 5 (October-November 1984)
    Folder 15: Volume 8 Number 6 (December 1984-January 1985)
    Folder 16: Volume 9 Number 1 (February-March 1985)
    Folder 17: Volume 9 Number 2 (April-May 1985)
    Folder 18: Volume 9 Number 3 (June-July 1985)
    Folder 19: Volume 9 Number 4 (August-September 1985)
    Folder 20: Volume 9 Number 5 (October-November 1985)
    Folder 21: undated (January-April 1983?)
    Folder 22: undated (June-July 1983?)
  - Logo., 1979.; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Logo design for SCWU's newsletter's "Letter to the Editor" by Carol Porter, Southern Chapter.
    Originally in black frame which was discarded during processing due to space considerations. Frame contained no evidential value.
  - Newsletters., 1977-1999.; 23 folders (Box 6, Folders 1 - 23)
    Folder 1: Volume 1 Number 6 (1977)
    Folder 2: Volume 2 Numbers 3-6 (1978)
    Folder 3: Volume 3 (1979)
    Folder 4: Volume 4 (1980)
    Folder 5: Volume 5 (1981)
    Folder 6: Volume 6 (1982)
    Folder 7: Volume 7 (1983)
    Folder 8: Volume 8 (1984)
    Folder 9: Volume 9 (1985)
    Folder 10: Volume 10 (1986)
    Folder 11: Volume 11 (1987)
    Folder 12: Volume 12 (1988)
    Folder 13: Volume 13 (1989)
    Folder 14: Volume 14 Numbers 1-2, 4-5 (1990)
    Folder 15: Volume 15 (1991)
    Folder 16: Volume 16 Numbers 1-2, 4-6 (1992)
    Folder 17: Volume 17 Numbers 3-5 (1993)
    Folder 18: Volume 18 Numbers 1-5 (1994)
    Folder 19: Volume 19 (1995)
    Folder 20: Volume 20 Numbers 2-5 (1996)
    Folder 21: Volume 21 Number 6 (1997)
    Folder 22: Volume 22 Number 9 (1998)
    Folder 23: November/December (1999)
    There are six issues to each newsletter volume. Unless otherwise listed, folders contain a complete volume for the year. Many folders also include duplicates of some issues.
  - Newsletters, bound., 1976-1987.; 5 folders (Boxes 6 - 7, Folders 24 - 25, 1 - 3)
    BOX 6
    Folder 24: Volumes 1-5 (1976-1981)
    Folder 25: Volume 1-Volume 7 Number 3, includes 7th Anniversary Issue, donated by June Mazer (1976-1983)
    BOX 7
    Folder 1: Volume 1-Volume 7 Number 3, includes 7th Anniversary issue, archival set (1976-1983)
    Folder 2: Volumes 6-9 (1982-1985)
    Folder 3: Volume 7 Number 4-Volume 11 Number 3, includes 10th Anniversary Issue (1983-1987)
  - Newsletter retrospective., 1976-1986.; 5 folders (Boxes 8 - 9, Folders 22 - 23, 1 - 3)
    BOX 8
    Folder 23: Landmarks and crises, first crisis (1976)
    Folder 24: Procedures evolution (1980-1986)
    BOX 9
    Folder 1: Distribution and circulation (1983)
    Folder 2: Budgets and finances (1980-1985)
    Folder 3: Advertising (1979-1985)
    Documents were originally compiled in a three-ring-binder labeled "Newsletter 1976-1986" by June Mazer.
  - Newsletter, tenth anniversary issue., 1986.; 1 folder (Boxes 9,15, Folder 4)
    Contains newsletter, galleys, and photographs.
    Contains three audio cassettes labeled "SCWU NL Brunch Founders 4/86 Tape 1," "SCWU NL Brunch Tape 2 4/86," and "NL Brunch Tape 3 4/86 Side one only, half."
    Material was originally compiled in a 3-ring-binder labeled "Newsletter: 10 year anniversary."
- Area chapters., 1979-1997.; Series 6.; 123.0 folders
  During the 1980s, Lesbian News hailed SCWU as the "largest lesbian organization in the country." The majority of its membership was concentrated in the southern California area between San Diego to Santa Barbara. In order to become a chapter, each group underwent a three step process from a formation group to steering committee to an area chapter. Each group functioned as a mini-SCWU in its area with its own committees, events, newsletter, and leadership; however, each group reported to the central Board of Directors and participated in organization-wide events. Each sub-series documents various aspects of area chapters' activities through committee minutes, flyers, newsletters, photographs, and other material on projects and events.
  - Beach Cities., 1985-1987.; Subseries 1.; 2.0 folders
    Contains event flyers and a SCWU newsletter clipping on the founding of the Beach Cities chapter.
    - Clipping., 1985.; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Flyers., 1982-1987.; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Desert., 1992.; Subseries 2.; 1.0 folder
    The folder is arranged in chronological order.
    Contains an event flyer.
    - Flyers., 1992.; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Inland., 1986-1989.; Subseries 3.; 3.0 folders
    Folders are in alphabetical order.
    Contains flyers, newsletters and a clipping from the SCWU newsletter on the founding of the Inland chapter.
    - Clipping., 1987.; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Flyers., undated.; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Newsletters., 1986-1989.; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Los Angeles/Valley., 1979-1994.; Subseries 4.; 58.0 folders
    Contains minutes and other materials from the education, election, and steering committees, correspondence (including circular letters), flyers, newsletters, photographs, and membership and employment information. The bulk of this sub-series consists of materials from two of the Education Committee's theater productions, "Lesbian Odyssey" and "Welcome to our Lesbian World." In addition to the script and other print materials for "Welcome to our Lesbian World," there is a beta video cassette of the production as well as two audio cassettes of the live performance.
    - Circular letters., 1979-1989.; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Committees., 1980-1993.; 3 folders (Box 12, Folders 55 - 57)
      BOX12
      Folder 55: Election (1984-1993)
      Folder 56: Miscellaneous (1981-1990), contains outline of committees' functions, retreat information, November 1983 membership meeting flyer, expense and income statements for March and May 1990, respectively.